freeadlists.com 2012-05-19

# Post Free Classified Ads - Other Cities In Mass Other Services Classifieds - Personals, Real Estate, Pets Ads Free Ads

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site ("Customers") and make use of the various services offered by FreeAdLists ("Services"). 

**"Personal Information"**   
Personal Information refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, profiles, social insurance number, and any other applicable forms of information. Personal Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual. 

**What Personal Information Is Collected?**   
We collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses of Customers and details of what the Customers intend to purchase or sell (Adverts). The basic user profile information is collected through the voluntary registration process. Any information provided by the user through the placement of an ad is completely voluntary and will be considered public information for public use, even if it is the same as that information collected in the registration process. FreeAdLists.com will not be liable or responsible for the use or distribution of information placed in an ad. 

**How is Personal Information Used?**   
We use Personal Information to customize the Site, to make service offers, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personal Information to contact Visitors and Customers in response to any inquiries, or to provide any information that is requested. 

**Who May Share Information?**

Personal Information about Customers may be shared with other Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions. We may share information about our Visitors, including the usage statistics of our Visitors and Customers, with our affiliates and third party vendors. We offer the opportunity for Visitors and Customers to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any of our affiliates. 

**How is Personal Information Kept?**   
Personal Information collected by FreeAdLists is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of FreeAdLists.com except for use as indicated in descriptions above. 

**What Choices do Visitors Have Regarding collection, use and distribution of such information?**   
Visitors and Customers can opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliates by contacting us via any of our specified email addresses. 

**Do We Use Cookies?**   
We do not use Cookies to obtain information about our Visitors and the services they select. We use Session based connections for security purposes and to protect our Customers as well. 

**How do We use login information?**   
FreeAdLists uses login information which may include but is not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze statistics, track a user's movement, administer the Site and gather other statistical information. 

**Can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personal Information?**   
Visitors and Customers may contact us to correct or update Personal Information about them by emailing as at any of our support email addresses. 

**Can Visitors delete or deactivate Personal Information collected by Us?**   
We allow Visitors and Customers to delete/deactivate Personal Information from the Site's database. This may be done by sending a request to support@FreeAdLists.com. Due to backups and records of deletions however, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. Anyone who requests to have their Personal Information deactivated will have this information deleted. 

**What about Privacy Policy Changes?**   
We let our Visitors and Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site when and where necessary. 

**Advertising services**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
